[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much did Harvard Universitys tuition and fees total for the 1958-1959 school year?", "correct_answer": "$1,250", "incorrect_answers": ["$2,925", "$3,225", "$5,110"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how many wild polar bears are estimated to live across the Arctic?", "correct_answer": "20,000", "incorrect_answers": ["100,000", "150,000", "60,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Traditionally the people of the country of Georgia believe that they are descendants of this Biblical personality.", "correct_answer": "Japheth", "incorrect_answers": ["Jonah", "Jesus", "Jeremiah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The seminal vesicle opens into which of the following?", "correct_answer": "urethra", "incorrect_answers": ["vas deferens", "cowpers gland", "penis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Buck Russell", "correct_answer": "Uncle Buck", "incorrect_answers": ["Mr. Mom", "Planes, Trains  Automobiles", "Shes Having a Baby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The city of Casablanca, which is the setting of the classic 1942 movie, starring Humphrey Bogart and Ingrid Bergman, is located in what African country?", "correct_answer": "Morocco", "incorrect_answers": ["Egypt", "Tunisia", "Algeria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie Adventures in Babysitting, what does Sarah leave in the back of Dans (the guy from the frat party) jeep?", "correct_answer": "Her skates", "incorrect_answers": ["Her backpack", "Her blanket", "Her candy bar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How are cockroaches classified according to the way they deliver their young?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They are viviparous.", "They are ovoviviparous.", "They are oviparous."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Epic of Gilgamesh is the oldest written story, containing a lot of references to the spirits of the dead.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average lifespan of Chihuahuas?", "correct_answer": "8- 18 years", "incorrect_answers": ["8 - 12 years", "8 - 26 years", "8 - 15 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Jake LaMottas wife in the movie Raging Bull?", "correct_answer": "Vicki", "incorrect_answers": ["Tracy Mc", "Patty", "Jennifer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Thai dish Khanom bueang is known under this name in the English-speaking world.", "correct_answer": "Crispy pancakes", "incorrect_answers": ["Spring rolls", "Yellow curry", "Curry puff"]}]